<resources>
    <string name="app_name">SRMCSE-RMPCampus</string>

    <string name="navigation_drawer_open">Open navigation drawer</string>
    <string name="navigation_drawer_close">Close navigation drawer</string>

    <string name="action_settings">Settings</string>
    <string name="OurDept"><![CDATA[
<html>
  <head>
   </head>
<body style=\"text-align:justify;color:gray;background-color:black;\">
        <p>Computer Science is a rapidly evolving discipline today. And at SRM, we go to great lengths to ensure that our faculty and students can devote themselves to take maximal advantage of modern computer science and engineering - to solve a wide range of complex scientific, technological and social problems.</p>
</body>
</html>
]]>

    </string>
    <string name="Abtdept"><![CDATA[
<html>
  <head>
   </head>
<body style=\"text-align:justify;color:gray;background-color:black;\">

        <b>About the department:</b>

       <p>
     The department of Computer Science and Engineering, Ramapuram has been flourishing since 2004. The department’s mission is to advance, evolve, and enhance computer science and fundamentals to build the intellectual capital of research and students. Incredible amenities for imparting training courses to engineering, students, community, etc. We strive for caliber in research, knowledge dissemination and societal transformation. We facilitate students with Wi-Fi and smart class rooms.
</p>

     </body>
</html>
]]>

    </string>
    <string name="Faculties"><![CDATA[
<html>
  <head>
   </head>
<body style=\"text-align:justify;color:gray;background-color:black;\">

<b>Faculties:</b>

      <p>
     The Department has well- proficient and experienced faculty members with the best available exposure to the ever embryonic horizon of computer field and their research work extends to publish in many reputed International Journals. The faculty members are expert in the areas of Data Mining and Warehousing, Network Security, Artificial Intelligence, Cloud Computing, Image Processing, Natural Language Processing, etc.
</p>

     </body>
</html>
]]>

    </string>
    <string name="lab"><![CDATA[
<html>
  <head>
   </head>
<body style=\"text-align:justify;color:gray;background-color:black;\">

<b>Laboratories:</b>

      <p>

     The Department has top-notched laboratories catering the needs of students. It provides a spectacular approach in various programming languages and enables to apply knowledge in latest Computer Technologies such as Mobile App Development, Robotics, Ethical hacking, Big data, High Speed Networks, Artificial Intelligence, Compiler Design.

</p>

     </body>
</html>
]]>

    </string>
</resources>
