<resources>
    <string name="app_name">SRMCSE-RMPCampus</string>

    <string name="navigation_drawer_open">Open navigation drawer</string>
    <string name="navigation_drawer_close">Close navigation drawer</string>

    <string name="action_settings">Settings</string>
    <string name="OurDept"><![CDATA[
<html>
  <head>
   </head>
<body style=\"text-align:justify;color:gray;background-color:black;\">
        <p>Computer Science is a rapidly evolving discipline today. And at SRM, we go to great lengths to ensure that our faculty and students can devote themselves to take maximal advantage of modern computer science and engineering - to solve a wide range of complex scientific, technological and social problems.</p>
</body>
</html>
]]>

    </string>
    <string name="OurVision"><![CDATA[
<html>
  <head>
   </head>
<body style=\"text-align:justify;color:gray;background-color:black;\">

        <b>Our Vision</b>

       <p> To offer up to date and flexible programs that will enable our graduates to be competitive in the job market. We strive to provide a hands-on approach in teaching computer related courses. And to this end, we are increasing the capacity of our computer laboratories as well as equipping them with the latest in hardware and software.</p>

     </body>
</html>
]]>

    </string>
    <string name="OurMission"><![CDATA[
<html>
  <head>
   </head>
<body style=\"text-align:justify;color:gray;background-color:black;\">

<b>Our Mission</b>

      <p>  To provide outstanding education and research training to our students - for productive careers in industry, academia, and the government. We strive for excellence in research, teaching and service, covering the fundamental as well as applied aspects of computer science. Our efforts include:</p>
 <p>   Establishing nationally and internationally recognized research programs, including those of interdisciplinary nature.
        Helping our students to develop the skills involved in solving complex technological problems of modern society.
        Providing a framework for promoting collaborative and multidisciplinary activities.
        At SRM University, the teaching environment is one that emphasizes depth, originality and critical thinking. The department also promotes innovative research and education programs in core computer science as well as multidisciplinary application areas. Upon graduation, our students will be able to perform research in all branches of the computing field.</p>

     </body>
</html>
]]>

    </string>
</resources>
